从创世之初起
Since the birth of time,
人类就尽力将坏人囚禁
humanity has endeavored to restrain evil men in prisons.
但自从该隐放跑了他的弑兄凶手之后
But since Cain fled the murder of his brother,
不断地有坏人逃离惩戒
evil men have fled the walls of punishment.
这样看来 即使你是个到处惹是生非 又在逃的混蛋
So, it doesn't matter if you're a badass motherfucker on the run,
也无关紧要 因为你自视优越
because you think you're better than everyone else,
觉得自己可以为所欲为
and somehow entitled to do what you gotta do.
那你就错了
No.
因为魔高一尺道高一丈
Because, you see, badass motherfuckers are never fast enough.
最终 他们都会自食其果
In the end, they will all be accounted for.
他妈的! 从哪儿冒出来的
Son of a bitch! Came out of nowhere.
- 她不是说他已经死了吗?  - 你看见他了?
- Didn't she say he was dead?  - You see him?
- 估计我们跟丢他了  - 我发誓她说过他已经死了
- I think we lost him.  - I swear she said he was dead.
- 睁大眼睛看着!  - 丫的还没死!
- Keep watching!  - Well, fucking he ain't!
- 开好你的车吧!  - 我他妈不正开着吗!
- Drive the fucking car!  - I'm driving the goddamn car!
看不到他啊
I don't see him.
他都知道 他知道我们对她做过些什么
He knows. He knows what we did to her.
他清楚得很! 他会来找我们报仇的!
He knows! He's gonna make us pay!
- 靠! 靠! 靠!  - 我觉得我们跟丢他了
- Shit! Shit! Shit!  - I think we lost him.
我不会告诉你他们把她带到哪儿去了 绝不
I ain't never telling you where they've taken her. Never.
我知道
I know.
你打断我的腿了 我操!
You took my leg, you fuck!
对不起 伙计
I'm sorry, man.
她在哪儿?
Where is she?
- 我不知道 伙计  - 那个小女孩在哪儿?
- I don't know, man.  - Where is the baby girl?
我不知道 伙计
I don't know, man.
我不知道
I don't know.
在Stillwater! 嘿! 嘿!
Stillwater! Hey! Hey!
在Deacon树林里的Stillwater沼泽地!
Okay, Deacon's Tree, man. Stillwater Marsh!
应该是在德州
Texas, I think.
你来晚了 你该知道的 是吧?
You're too late. You gotta know that, right?
月圆之夜 就是她丧命之时
First full moon, she's dead, man.
她死后 地狱里的人就会来到该死的地球上
She's dead and hell's gonna walk the motherfucking earth.
地狱里的人已经来到地球上了
Hell already is walking the earth.
你去告诉他 我就来 告诉他我要去把她夺回来
You tell him I'm coming. Tell him I'm coming to get her back.
# 让一切见鬼 让一切见鬼 让一切见鬼去吧 #
# Raise a little hell, raise a little hell. Raise a little hell. #
然后 我就告诉他 我说 "Frank 到此为止 我不再供应免费牛奶了
So, I tell him, I says, "Frank, that's it. No more free milk.
你得买下这头奶牛 你个狗娘养的"
You gonna have to buy the cow, you son of a bitch."
但你没那么胖吧 Piper
But you are not fat, Piper.
什么? 不是啦 Norma Jean "买下这头奶牛"是让他娶我的意思
What? No, Norma Jean. "Buy the cow." Marry me.
我是让他娶我 否则不和他上床
I'm saying he's gotta marry me. I cut him off.
不和他上床?
You cut him off?
是的 千真万确!
Not just yes, but hell, yes!
不准抓咪咪 不准摸屁屁 我还跟他说
No tits, no ass, and I told him,
"要是再把你的老二往我脸上凑
"If I see that big ol' dick anywhere near my face again,
- 我就一口咬断它"  - 你真这么说了?
- I'm gonna bite it in half."  - You said that?
没错 真说了
Yeah, sure did.
哦 天呐 这样多久了?
Oh, my God. How long has it been?
哦 两天 但对他那种无性不欢的人来说 像十年之久
Oh, two days. But that's like a decade in horny fucker years.
那他给你买钻戒了吗?
So, he bought you a diamond?
哦 天呐 没 要是Frank有钱给我买钻戒
Oh, God, no. If Frank had money for a diamond,
我老早就让他爽翻天了
I would have jacked his sorry ass ages ago and put this shit hole in rear view.
不过他确实单膝下跪向我求婚了
But he did get down on one knee and ask me to be his bride.
- 不是吧! 哦!  - 是的哦!
- No way! Oh!  - Yes, way!
亲爱的!
Honey!
够了 够了!
Come on, come on!
你们觉得我付薪水 就是让你们站着闲聊的?
You think I pay you bitches to stand around and yap?
给我回去工作
Get the fuck back to work.
干死你啊
Sit on it, baby.
嗨 你们好 我叫Piper 要些什么喝的吗?
Hi, guys. I'm Piper. Can I get you something to drink?
我们要这个
We'll take this.
"砖房"早餐 里面有10份大薄煎饼 一共是4.99美元
"She's a Brickhouse" breakfast. Ten monster flapjacks for $4.99.
- 加三杯水  - 好的 还要些其它...
- And three waters.  - All right, and what can I get for...
就要这些 薄煎饼就行了 没问题吧
That's it. Just the pancakes, if that's okay.
好的 马上就来
Okay, coming right up.
Lou 一份砖房套餐!
Lou, one Brickhouse!
好啊 帅哥 要喝咖啡吗?
Hello, beautiful. Coffee?
清咖啡 加糖
Black, with sugar.
你听说过Stillwater沼泽或者一个叫做Deacon树林的地方吗? 貌似在德州?
Have you ever heard of a Stillwater Marsh or a Deacon's Tree? In Texas, maybe?
Stillwater沼泽 有啊 我听说过
Stillwater Marsh, yeah, I've heard of it,
但它不在德州
but it ain't in Texas.
Stillwater在路易斯安那州
Stillwater is in Louisiana.
是个小镇吗?
Small town?
亲爱的 Stillwater是座监狱
Honey, Stillwater is a prison.
我老爸在那儿待过一阵子 后来那儿就关了
My daddy did some time there before it closed.
我去帮你准备咖啡
I'll get you that coffee.
给 松饼和热牛奶
Here's some muffins and warm milk.
- 可我们没点...  - 这些是免费的
- But we didn't order...  - It's on the house.
你不想知道我什么时候下班吗?
So, you gonna ask me what time my shift ends?
今晚是月圆之夜哦
It's a full moon tonight.
每当月圆之夜我就有点儿饥渴
I always feel a little randy with a full moon.
我在月圆的这两天禁欲
Full moon's two days off.
你肯定吗 亲爱的?
You sure about that, sweetie?
非常肯定
Pretty sure.
外面那辆跑车不错 是你的吗?
Now, that's a hell of a ride out there. Is that yours?
那辆道奇吗? 我倒想啊
The Charger? I wish.
是她的吗?
Is it hers?
来了 这是你们要的水
All right, here are them waters.
薄煎饼稍后送上
I'll be right back with the flapjacks.
是的 不过如果你想上...
Sure. But if you're looking for a ride...
我跟你说过要加糖的
I told you I wanted sugar.
我们请客? 丫的我们请客?
On the house? On the fucking house?
别紧张 反正我们也准备把那些松饼扔掉了
Relax. We gonna throw them muffins out, anyway.
如果他们不付钱的话 那有人就得代劳了
If they're not gonna pay for them, somebody's gonna have to pay the price.
死胖子 我告诉过你不准再那样碰我的
I told you, you fat fuck son of a bitch, never touch me like that again.
- 放开我的蛋蛋  - 闭嘴
- Let go of my balls.  - Shut up.
松饼钱算我的 老娘不干了
Muffins are on me. I quit.
在松饼上涂些蜂蜜和黄油 那样会更好吃
Put some honey butter on them muffins. They'll taste an awful lot better that way.
# 留恋我的胸前说你要我 低吟我的名字 一如既往 #
# Sucking on my titties like you wanted me, calling me all the time. #
# 就像金发女郎 看看命中注定那个他是否伸手可及 习以为常#
# Like Blondie, check out my Chrissy behind. It's fine all of the time. #
# 认识新的小妞儿你又能做什么 哈 #
# What else is in the teaches of Peaches, huh? #
# 说什么? #
# What? #
# 去他妈的伤痛 去他妈的伤痛 #
# Fuck the pain away. Fuck the pain away #
# 去他妈的伤痛 #
# Fuck the pain away #
# 去他妈的伤痛 去他妈的伤痛 #
# Fuck the pain away. Fuck the pain away #
# 去他妈的伤痛 #
# Fuck the pain away #
哦! 操!
Oh! Motherfuck!
现在看来 不算太糟
Now, that's not so bad.
如果你愿意 我可以帮你修
I can fix that if you'd like.
好啊 谢谢
I would. Thank you.
前提是你得捎我一段
If you give me a lift.
我只能把你带到Blackfoot瀑布 那里有车会停
I'm only going as far as Blackfoot Falls. The truck stop there.
那也感激不尽
I'd be much obliged.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得申明一下
Just so you know,
我从不载伸手拦车的客人
I don't pick up hitchhikers.
我也没伸手说拦车啊
I didn't have my thumb out.
要帮忙吗?
Need some help there?
你 胖子 过来下
You, fat fuck. Come here.
你叫我什么? 你刚刚叫我什么?
What'd you call me? What did you just call me?
我叫你"胖子" 现在不是说这个的时候
I called you "fat fuck." And we had better leave it at that.
除非你想让我叫你"死胖子"
Unless you'd prefer I call you "dead fat fuck."
什么?
What?
我在找一个人 40岁左右 身高2米多
I'm looking for someone. Maybe 40 or so, 6'1",
看上去不像本地人的样子
probably looked out of place.
啊!
Ah!
他之前来过这儿 没带什么行李
He was here earlier. Traveling light.
- 或许是步行来的  - 你是谁?
- Likely on foot.  - Who are you?
我是"会计师"
I'm The Accountant.
跟我说这个有什么用吗?
That supposed to mean something to me?
要是我把你的名字写进名册 你就知道有用了 如果你不告诉我 我想要的信息...
It will if I add you to the books. And if you don't tell me what I want to know...
你想说什么?
You had something to say?
他之前来过这儿
He was here. Earlier.
- 他去哪儿了?  - 往那边走了
- Where did he go?  - That way.
是步行的
On foot.
多谢你载我这程
I appreciate the ride.
你没事吧?
You all right?
没事 只是 我辞职了 再一次
Yeah. I mean, I quit my job. Again.
但这一次不同于以往 因为...
But this time it's different 'cause...
我不知道 我男人失业了 而我们刚刚订了婚
I don't know, my man's out of work and we just got engaged.
他是个好人吗?
Is he a good man?
是的
Yeah.
是的 他挺好的 呃 这些事自己心中总是有数的
Yeah, he is. I mean, I guess you can just tell these things.
- 不不不 该死!  - 亲爱的 我干得正爽呢
- No, no, no. Fuck!  - Baby, I'm fucking you all right.
- 耶  - 先别干了...
- Yeah.  - No fucking...
你他妈的知道自己在做什么吗? 你个疯婆娘
What the hell do you think you're doing? Psycho bitch.
Piper Piper 听我解释 她只是在给我看些东西
Piper, Piper, I can explain. She was just showing me something.
滚出去! 你敢
Get out! Don't.
去死吧 Piper 我们正在...
Fuck you, Piper. We're in...
我听不清你说什么!
I didn't quite hear what you said!
我说 "我们正在..."
I said, "We're in..."
是你逼我出轨的 都是你的错
You made me cheat on you. This is your fault.
- 你能...  - 嘿!
- Would you...  - Hey!
Piper 站住!
Piper, stop!
你没别的地方去啊 你心里明白
You've got nowhere else to go, and you know it.
哦 宝贝 你以为我在佛罗里达找不到比你更好的男人了吗?
Oh, baby. You don't think I can find a guy better than you in Florida?
佛罗里达? 肯定没了 德州? 或许还有点希望
Florida? Hell, no. Texas? Maybe.
那就等着瞧吧
We'll see about that.
不不不 你不能开走我的车
No, no, no. You're not taking my car.
你不能开走我的车 贱人!
You're not taking my car, bitch!
你的车? 是谁在付账单啊
Your car? Who's been making the payments,
你个连工作都没有 只会操Mona没用的畜生?
you out of work, skanky, Mona-fucking piece of shit?
你疯了吧 死女人
You're insane, woman.
你看你逼我做了什么! 起来 我去帮你敷点冰块
Look what you made me do! Come on. I'll get you some ice.
Frank 亲爱的
Frank, sweetie.
我要告诉大家 我是如何亲眼看见你玩弄我的粉色假阳具
I'm gonna tell everybody what I caught you doing with my pink dildo.
你不想和我在一起了?
You don't wanna be with me?
好吧 我来帮你 让你永远都没男人要 永远没有
Fine. When I'm done, nobody's gonna wanna be with you, ever.
- 去死吧  - 哈!
- Go to hell.  - Ha!
嘿
Hey.
我的世界暗无天日
I am one with the darkness.
我的世界暗无天日 我的世界暗无天日
I am one with the darkness. I am one with the darkness.
黑暗笼罩着我
It bums through me.
黑暗笼罩着我 现在向你们袭来了
It bums through me. Now to you.
将我们联系在一起
Forge our bond together.
只有交出祭品
And offer the sacrifice
才能我们获得自由
that will set us all free.
我们才能走出这死亡之谷的阴影
We will walk through the valley of the shadow of death.
不!
No!
不! 求你了 不要带走我的孩子
No! Please, don't take my baby.
只有经过...
And only through...
- 把孩子给我  - 不!
- Give me the baby.  - No!
要我把窗拉上吗?
You want me to roll up the window?
不用
No.
如果冷的话可以披上我的夹克
You can use my jacket if you're cold.
谢谢
Thank you.
你没把他打死吧?
You didn't kill him, did you?
Your fiancé? No.
你的未婚夫吗? 没有
谢谢你
Thanks for that.
你饿吗?
Are you hungry?
喝点东西就行了
I could use a drink.
你来自俄克拉荷马州?
Oklahoma?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
你提到佛罗里达
You mentioned Florida.
我在路易斯安那州做生意 能带我去那儿吗?
My business is in Louisiana. Can you get me that far?
- 什么生意?  - 我在找一个人
- What business?  - I'm looking for someone.
我叫Milton
I'm Milton.
你叫Piper是吧?
You're Piper, right?
Milton 你要是想把我杀了 扔进小树林
Well, Milton, if you try and kill me and dump me in the woods,
我就废了你的老二
I'm gonna cut your nuts off.
遵命 小姐
Yes, Ma'am.
那就好
All right, then.
猛牛酒吧
# 所有飞机都已着陆... #
# All the planes have been grounded... #
晚上好 朋友们 欢迎来到猛牛酒吧
Greetings, folks. Welcome to the Bull By The Balls.
嘿 Roy
Roy.
Milton啊
Milton.
我还以为你死了
Thought you were dead.
是你希望我死了 这不一样
You hoped I was dead. Not the same.
你准备今晚住这儿?
You planning on staying?
有问题吗?
You got a problem with that?
但愿你带够钱了
Your money's good as any, I expect.
不过天亮之前就得离开
But be gone by dawn.
# 那个就被叫做睡精灵 #
# That goes by the name of the sandman #
你们刚才在说些什么?
What was that all about?
我的另一种生活 那时我经常开车经过这里
In another life, I used to drive a truck through these parts.
我喜欢来见他妹妹
I'd enjoy a visit with his sister.
- 然后他生气了?  - 对
- And he took offense?  - Yes.
- 怎么了?  - 没事
- What's wrong?  - Nothing.
- 真的?  - 你好
- You sure?  - Howdy.
我叫Candy
I'm Candy.
要不要先喝点什么?
Start you off with some drinks?
- 啤酒  - 我也是
- Beer.  - Same.
我还要看看身份证才行
I need to see some IDs, too.
这是在搞什么?
What the hell is this?
我想你有阵子没来这儿了吧
Guess it's been a while since you did that visiting.
要喝东西? 得先入会 必须是Dry郡的人
You want a drink? You gotta be a member. Dry county.
哦 妈的 对不起
Oh, shit. Sorry.
- 那是我的东西  - 别用那种看小偷的眼神看着我
- That was in my pocket.  - Don't look at me like I'm some sort of thief.
我拿走它是想有个保障
I lifted it for protection.
要是你偷走我的车
If you stole my ride,
到天边我也要抓到你
I was gonna have to hunt you down.
她说的话很好笑吗?
Did she say something funny?
是啊 这驾照岂止是过期 都能算得上是古董了
Yeah, this license isn't just expired, it's antique.
那好吧 给我一杯清咖啡 加糖
All right, then bring me a black coffee with sugar.
哦! 好啦 好啦 好啦 只对你哦 帅哥
Aw! Now, now, now. For you, handsome,
或许吧 我可能要破一次例了
I don't know, I think maybe I can bend the rules a bit.
别告诉别人
Don't tell nobody.
你要上她吗?
You gonna tap that or what?
上谁?
Tap?
天啊 Milton 才过多久你就不记得她了?
Geez, Milton, how long has it been?
我脑子里装满了别的事
I've had a lot on my mind.
啊哈 好吧 随你便了
Uh-huh. Right. Suit yourself then.
不过要知道没人会在临死前说 "我后悔我做爱做得太多"
But no one ever reaches the end and says, "l wish I hadn't fucked so much."
你要到哪去?
Where you going?
我要去洗个澡 躺到温暖的大床上
I'm going to take a shower, lie in a warm bed,
- 修修脚趾甲  - 你啤酒不要了吗?
- do my nails.  - What about your beer?
你喝吧 天亮再见
You drink it. I'll see you at dawn.
这是你的 大男孩
Here you go, big boy.
# 像一只在飓风中被抛弃的鹰 #
# Like an eagle in the eye of a hurricane that's abandoned #
老兄 要喝一杯吗?
Get you a drink, friend?
你这个地方不错
It's a nice place you got.
你这场地可以出租开派对 是吧?
You rent that out for parties here?
当然 你想开派对?
We sure do. You planning a party?
对 我今晚就想开一个
Yeah. I'm planning on having one of them tonight.
自称预言家的教士Jonah King...
Reverend Jonah King, the self-proclaimed prophet...
妈妈 妈妈 听着 我跟她结束了
Mom, Mom, look, it's over.
Piper走了 我只想要回我的车
Piper's gone. I just want my car back.
- 听着 我要挂了 警察来了 - 被传到警局录...
- Look, I gotta go. Cops are here.  - are wanted for questioning...
- 我也爱你  - 关于一对年轻夫妇谋杀案的口供
- I love you, too.  - in the brutal murder of the young parents.
他妈的这么久才来
About fucking time.
- 我早就打你们电话了...  - 有一个旅行者
- I called you guys like...  - There was a traveler.
- 两米多高  - 什么?
- 6'1".  - What?
啊! 对 是那个旅行者
Ah! Yes, the traveler.
态度恶劣
Angry with attitude.
之前打我的那个畜生... 你是谁?
Sumbitch kicked me in the... Who are you?
- 我是"会计师"  - 会计...
- I'm The Accountant.  - The...
我叫的是警察
I called a cop.
那个"畜生"
The "sumbitch",
他去了哪儿?
where did he go?
他妈的我怎么知道? 我醒来之后三个都不见了
Fuck should I know? I woke up and all three were gone.
- 三个?  - 那个婊子 那个畜生
- All three?  - The bitch, the sumbitch
- 还有我的车!  - 什么样的车?
- and my car!  - What kind of car?
听着 Hugo Boss(德国著名服装品牌)先生
Look, Hugo Boss,
你不是警察 那我就无可奉告了
you ain't no cop, me ain't no talking.
一天连续碰到两个畜生? 是你逼我的
Two sumbitches in one day? You leave me no choice.
我要用这根肯塔基的棍子打到你屁股开花
I'm gonna take this stick from Kentucky and beat your ass with it.
- 什么样的车 Frank?  - 什么?
- What kind of car, Frank?  - What?
你的车 是什么样的?
Your car, what kind is it?
为什么受伤的总是我?
Why does everyone keep hurting me?
回答 我的
Answer. The.
问题
Question.
69年的道奇 你个混蛋
'69 Charger, you fuck.
引擎是440型的还是半球型的?
440 or the Hemi?
440的
440.
等等 等等 等等 把我放下来 求你了 不!
Wait, wait, wait. Get me off this wall. Please. No!
你要上哪儿去? 求求你 放我下来!
Where you going? Please, get me off the wall.
嘿 王八蛋 那是我的照片
Hey, fuck tard, that's mine.
白痴 笨蛋 那是...
Shithead, shithead, that's...
- 是你报警说自己车丢了?  - 你是Frank Raimi吗?
- You call about a stolen car?  - Frank Raimi?
他在里面
In there.
我在找一个人 身高两米多 不是本地人
I'm looking for someone. 6'1", not from around here.
他开着一辆69年的道奇车
He's driving a '69 Charger.
他和这个女人在一起
He's traveling with her.
天呐
Jesus.
- 你说什么?  - 把手举到头顶上
- Excuse me?  - Keep your hands where I can see them.
举起手来 混蛋
Show me your hands, asshole.
- 今天是你们的幸运日  - 什么意思...
- This is your lucky day.  - What's the matter...
你是...
You're...
你是联邦调查员?
you're a Fed?
我在追捕一名逃犯 John John Milton
I'm in pursuit of a traveler. John, John Milton.
他和照片中的这个女孩在一起
He's with the girl in this photo.
- 但屋子里的这家伙 他...  - 死了 是
- But the guy in the room, he's...  - Dead. Yes.
如果我说这太不幸了 那肯定是撒谎
I'd say it's unfortunate, but I'd be lying.
除了他妈妈 没人会想念他
Only his mother will miss him.
听着 警官们 我需要你们帮忙追捕这名逃犯
Look, troopers, I need your help with my pursuit of this fugitive.
如果我们三个能够抓到他...
If we three could apprehend him...
- 你们都有雄心壮志吧  - 算是有
- You are ambitious.  - I guess.
当然 我们胸怀大志
Yes, we are.
我能看出来你们有
I can tell that you are.
成功了就意味着升职 加薪 我他妈向你们保证
Success will mean promotion, pay raise. I guaran-fucking-tee it.
现在 我们去抓这个Milton吧
Now, we are going to hunt this Milton.
我们要先找到他开的那辆道奇车
We are going to find the Charger that he's driving
一找到他 你们就开枪打死他
and when we find him, you will shoot to kill.
是开枪打死他
Shoot to kill.
这样做是非法的
That's against protocol.
是 但这个人特别危险
Yeah. This man is highly dangerous.
他已经杀过人了 他还会继续滥杀无辜 一经发现就要把他处决掉
He has killed. He will kill again. He must be taken down on sight.
否则你们还没走完你们的法律程序
The time it takes you to follow your protocols,
他已经取走你们的性命了
that's the time it takes him to end your life.
可以走了吗?
Shall we?
来吧
Come on.
- 哦! 操 爽呆了!  - 呃 我们也会做那个吗?
- Oh! Fuck, yeah!  - Um, are we gonna do it?
那要看你把我趾甲染得好不好了
Depends on how well you do those nails.
哦!
Oh!
看吧 你小心点 这个趾甲要重染了
See, you gotta be careful. You're gonna have to redo that one.
哦 耶 哦 耶 哦 我的天呐!
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, my God!
对不起 你他妈的给我闭嘴! 听到了吗! 闭上你的鸟嘴!
Sorry. Shut the fuck up in there! Come on! Shut the fuck up!
动一动 把你的鸡巴动起来
Move it. You can move that cock.
哦! 真该死
Oh! God damn it.
刚才对不起了
Sorry about that.
来啊 快点 动起来
Come on. Come on, move it.
等一等
Hang on.
三月十五日 在一家当地的脱衣舞夜总会后面的垃圾车里
March 15th, in a dumpster behind a local strip club.
本案定于2011年二月审判
The case is set to go to trial in February of 2011.
来看另一条新闻
In other news tonight,
科罗拉多婴儿失踪案有了新线索
new details are emerging in the case of a missing Colorado infant.
联邦调查员会同科罗拉多州警局
Investigators, in cooperation with the Colorado state police,
发出了一份即刻逮捕Jonah King的全面通缉令
have issued an all points bulletin for Jonah King's immediate detention
罪名是谋杀科罗拉多州拉弗兰市一对年轻夫妇
in connection with the murders of a young married couple in Loveland, Colorado.
他们的女婴被认为遭到这名宗教狂热分子的绑架
Their infant girl is believed to have been abducted by this religious sect.
全国范围内的安珀警报(协助寻找被诱拐儿童的预警机制)已经全面启动
A nationwide Amber Alert is now in full effect.
你们可能还记得 这出悲剧是这样开始的 那位年轻的母亲...
You may recall we broke the story first that the young mother...
联邦调查员拒绝发表评论
Investigators refuse to comment.
尽管如此 我们的记者Nathan Brown近期已经了解到...
Although, our own Nathan Brown has recently learned...
看看这个帅气的魔鬼
Look at that handsome devil.
这些笨蛋们哪会知道 能看到下一个时代的救世主 是件多么荣幸的事
Fools do not know how blessed they are to look upon the messiah of the next age.
那个女的在11号房间 而Milton
The girl is in 11. And Milton,
在12号
he's in number 12.
这个Milton绝不是我们的同僚
This Milton is no friend to us.
他会千方百计阻止我们得到应得的东西
He will try and keep us from what we are rightfully owed.
他就是荒漠
He is the blight,
而我们则是甘霖
and we are the rain.
快去 把你们的怨气都撒到他身上
Go forth and pour your anger upon him.
哦 耶
Oh, yeah.
哦 宝贝 你为什么不脱光衣服?
Oh, baby. Why don't you fuck naked?
我从不光着身子迎接枪战
I never disrobe before a gunfight.
哦 耶
Oh, yeah.
# 我知道你想要蜜糖 #
# I know that you want the candy #
# 给我从未尝过的蜜糖 #
# Gimme candy I've never had #
# 尝起来太甜 把美好的爱都变坏 #
# Tastes so sweet, makes good love bad #
# 没有了我的爱 #
# Fallen out with my love #
# 一分一秒都很难挨 #
# A grievous time to pass #
# 没了糖让我心伤 #
# Sugar done break my heart #
# 我的情也无法久长 #
# A heart not meant to last #
# 纵然在黯淡的日子里... #
# In spite of saddened days... #
来吧 宝贝 别客气
Come on, baby. Don't be shy.
你的宝贝就要死了
That baby is as good as dead.
哦 爽呆了!
Oh, fuck yeah!
操! 操!
Shit! Shit!
收拾他 混账东西! 教训他 谁才是他妈的混蛋?
Fuck him, motherfucker! Fuck him. Who's a punk-ass motherfucker?
# 我知道你想要蜜糖 #
# I know that you want the candy #
# 给我从未尝过的蜜糖 #
# Gimme candy I've never had #
# 尝起来太甜 把美好的爱都变坏 #
# Tastes so sweet, makes good love bad #
哦 该死
Oh, hen.
你能冷静点吗?
Would you calm down?
很明显 他被利用了
He definitely took the bait.
- 你认识这些人?  - 我们得赶紧离开 可能有更多人会来
- You know these people?  - We should hurry. There are probably more.
看 那是Jonah King
Look, there's Jonah King.
警官们 记住我们来这儿的目的
Troopers, remember why we're here.
Milton啊
Milton.
Milton 你必须告诉我这是怎么回事
Milton, you owe me some answers.
是他
It's him.
别动!
Freeze!
Milton! 操!
Milton! Fuck!
升职加薪 升职加薪
Promotion and pay raise. Promotion and pay raise.
头低下!
Get down!
放下枪!
Drop in!
- 不!  - 你会后悔的 畜...
- No!  - You sorry mother...
操! 去死吧你...
Fuck you!  Die, you...
噢 上帝
Oh, my God.
- Milton 你要干什么?  - 我去追他
- Milton, what are you doing?  - I'm going after him.
怎么? 想和我一起吗?
Why? You wanna join me?
血差不多止住了
Bleeding's almost stopped.
只是擦伤而已
It's just a graze.
Milton 那些警察没事先警告就向我们开枪
Milton, those cops shot at us with no warning.
他们不是想抓我们 是想杀了我们
They weren't trying to arrest us, they were trying to kill us.
他们想杀了你
They were trying to kill you.
什么 你是个杀人犯? 你逃狱了还是怎样?
What, are you a murderer? You escape from prison or something?
- 说 是什么?  - 全中
- Go on, what is it?  - Both.
天呐 我做了些什么?
Jesus, what have I done?
你他妈的为什么要把我牵扯进来? Milton 我杀了个警察!
What have you fucking got me in to? Milton, I shot a cop!
我会被抓去坐牢! 你明白吗? 操!
I'm gonna go to jail! Do you understand that? Fuck!
给我个不爆你头的理由
Give me one good reason I shouldn't shoot you in the face.
我在开车
I'm driving.
你懂我意思的!
You know what I mean!
操!
Fuck!
他们带走了她的孩子
They took her baby.
他们带走了她的小女儿
They took her little girl.
新闻上报道的那个小女孩?
The little girl on the news?
- 大家都在找的小孩?  - 是的
- The little baby everyone's looking for? - Yes.
他们杀了我女儿 带走了她孩子
They killed my daughter. They took her baby.
这小女孩是我的全部
That baby girl is all I got.
她是我与女儿的唯一关联
She's the last connection to my daughter.
我要把她找回来
I am going to get her back.
用猎枪 子弹已经装上了
Shotgun. It's already loaded.
把车窗摇下来
Roll it down.
就是现在!
Now!
把另一枝枪准备好
Get the other gun ready.
不 不 不 那支旧的 箱子里那支 把它准备好
No, no, no. The old one. The big one in the case, have it ready.
已经...
It's...
已经结束了 Milton 停车
It's over, Milton. Stop the car.
- 我可不能那么做!  - 是吗?
- I can't do that!  - Really?
你怎么会认为自己还有得选?
What makes you think you have a choice?
首先 因为你很惹人厌
Because you're obnoxious, first,
另外 我还有点事要做
and because I have something I gotta do.
那你本该提前做好的
Well, then you should've done it a long time ago.
我没必要提前做好 是吧?
I didn't have to do it a long time ago, did I?
噢 Milton 为了接近你 我可是会杀了你后座上那个漂亮小妞儿的哦
Oh, Milton, I will kill that pretty little woman in the backseat to get to you.
你以为你是Loki?(制造不和与灾难的火神)
You think you're Loki, huh?
你以为你是星期六男爵(巫毒教的死神)吗?
You think you're Baron Samedi?
- 我不会让它发生的  - 再重复一遍
- I won't allow that.  - Again,
你怎么会认为自己还有得选的?
what makes you think you have a choice?
因为它
This does.
Piper 等等!
Piper, wait!
他不是杀你女儿的凶手之一 是吧?
He ain't one of them that killed your daughter, was he?
他是另外的人
He's someone else.
有谁不想要你的命吗?
Anyone not trying to kill you?
没有
No.
你那是把什么枪?
What kind of fucking gun is that?
和你用的枪一样
The kind you use on guys like that.
我得装弹 你来开车
I need to reload. You drive.
操蛋
God damn it.
你 你! 你不能待在这儿
You. You! You can't be here.
- Rookie!  - Sarge 这老头子
- Rookie!  - Sarge, this old joke,
他不能在犯罪现场四周走来走去
he can't stomp around the crime scene.
队长 很抱歉
Captain, sorry about that.
Sarge 你最好让家这伙立马给我滚蛋
Sarge, you'd better get this guy out of here right now.
队长 他还是新人
Cap, he's green, that's all.
他现在就站在证据上面
Standing on evidence is what he's doing.
0.45英寸口径
0.45s.
- 把它们装好贴上标签  - 是 长官
- Bag them and tag them.  - Yes, sir.
- 嘿 把这些包起来  - Sarge.
- Hey, Tag these.  - Sarge.
为什么会有两个科罗拉多州的警察
Why do we have two dead Colorado troopers
死在我们伟大的俄克拉荷马州?
within our great state of Oklahoma?
这两位先生怎么会与人意见不合 而惨遭杀身之祸呢?
And how did these gentlemen come to be on the wrong end of a disagreement?
房间里的住客 John Milton 听说不在死亡名单之列?
The guest in this room, John Milton, I take it he's not among the departed?
- 没错 长官  - 队长 找到个活的
- No, sir.  - Cap, we got a live one.
设置路障 Sarge 遍布全国 你知道该怎么做
I want roadblocks, Sarge. All over the state. You know the drill.
拿条毯子 再叫个医生过来
Get me a blanket and get a medic in here, too.
你现在好些了吧
You're gonna be okay now.
我们在做爱
We was fucking.
他杀了他 就在我们做爱之时!
He killed him while we was fucking!
- 谁干的?  - 不 你不明白
- Who did?  - No, you don't understand.
我从未遇到过这种事 你知道吗?
It's never happened to me before, you know?
你遇到过吗?
Has it ever happened to you?
另外再找个精神科医生过来
Let's get a shrink in here, too.
伙计
Dude,
你觉得车下面会有人吗?
you think there's anybody in there?
恐怕是的
I guess.
门还关着在
The doors are still closed.
- 上帝啊...  - 我是上帝的老爹
- Jesus...  - Carpenter.
你听到那些都不算数 他更喜欢短发
And despite what you've heard, prefers short hair.
你他妈的差点弄死我 伙计
You almost fucking killed me, man.
没那么严重
Not even close.
你73岁前我都不会再见到你
I won't see you again until you're 73.
你 我们三个月后见
You, I'll see in three months.
嘿 那话什么意思?
Hey, what does that mean?
我女儿一毕业就和King混在一起
My daughter got mixed up with King straight out of college.
她认识他? 她认识Jonah King?
She knew him? She knew Jonah King?
她认识他 是的 没错 她认识
She knew him, yes, yes, she did.
她的世界就陷入了一片混乱
Her world was in a tailspin,
King一直在宣扬静默革命
and King was preaching quiet revolution.
过了4个月 她才发觉所谓的"静默"就是
It was four months before she realized "quiet" meant hiding
躲在地下室 斩鸡头 洒鸡血
in a basement, cutting the heads off of chickens.
Jonah King会巫术?
Jonah King's into voodoo?
不是巫术 是黑魔法
Not voodoo, satanic magic.
他在为自己的末日决战招兵买马
He was recruiting for his own personal Armageddon.
自然 我女儿想退出
Understandably, my daughter wanted out.
当她告诉他 她要离开时
When she told him she was leaving,
他用个轮胎铁圈把她的腿打断了三处
he broke her leg in three places with a tire iron.
天啦
Jesus.
她得到了教训
She learned her lesson,
乖乖当了18个月的小追随者 然后一天夜里
was a good little follower for 18 months, then one night,
她趁Jonah独自一人时 用五角挂饰
she got Jonah alone and stabbed him in his face
刺伤了他的脸
with a pentagram pendant,
自己就消失在了黑暗中
and vanished into the darkness.
Milton 你女儿在邪教待了两年
Milton, your daughter was in a cult for two years,
你居然对此一无所知?
and you didn't even know about it?
我是说 之前你为什么不帮她?
I mean, why didn't you help her before?
我对此毫不知情 直到...
I didn't find out about any of this until...
直到我被监禁之后
Until after I got locked up.
你不上膛了?
You're not gonna reload?
总共只能装三枚子弹
Only three bullets to begin.
Milton 那是他的面包车
Milton, that's his van.
靠边停车
Pull over.
待这儿
Stay here.
# 每朵花儿都盛放 每只鸟儿都歌唱 #
# Each little flower that opens Each little bird that sings #
# 一切明亮又美好 生灵伟大又渺小 #
# All things bright and beautiful All creatures great and small #
# 万物聪慧又精彩 都是上帝的功劳 #
# All things wise and wonderful The Lord God made them all #
# 一切明亮又美好 #
# All things bright and beautiful #
# 生灵伟大又渺小 #
# All creatures great and small #
老兄 换做我是你 决不会这么做
Man, I wouldn't do that if I were you.
放她走 然后把小孩给我
Let her go and give me the child.
否则我让你们全都人头落地
Or I'll blow all your heads off.
放下枪 不然我们干掉她
Drop it. Or we will gut her.
你自己选 宝贝 不过不管怎样 我们都赢定了
Your choice, sugar. But either way, we win.
这不是闹着玩 伙计
We don't play, boy.
Milton 是吧?
Milton, isn't it?
你怎么在这儿?
Why you here?
- 为什么你这么小题大作?  - 你知道我为什么来这
- Why you making such a fuss?  - You know why I'm here.
我只知道
All I know about you is
你抛弃了你女儿
you abandoned your daughter.
她失望透顶 所以告诉大家你死了
Crushed her so completely, she told everyone you were dead.
不 Milton
No, Milton.
出于好意 我不能把这孩子给你
I cannot, in good faith, hand over this child to you.
那在月圆之夜牺牲她就是可以了吗?
But sacrificing her under the full moon is okay?
这孩子受到神难以置信的青睐
This child is unbelievably blessed.
看看你周围 世界水深火热
Look around you. World is on fire.
人们都在忍受煎熬
People are suffering.
除非爆发革命 不然他们将继续受苦
And they will continue to suffer until change comes.
继续放声大笑吧 孩子
Yeah, go ahead and laugh, boy.
革命即将到来
Change is gonna come.
多亏了你的血统
Thanks to your lineage.
这孩子将会开启一扇通往新的
This child will open the door to a new
世界秩序的大门
world order.
你这个骗子杀了我女儿 还想跟我宣扬这些狗屁宗教
The charlatan murders my daughter and then feeds me his philosophy.
你女儿的死是个意外
Your daughter's death was an accident.
我全都看到了
I saw the whole thing.
我看到了四下无人时 你真正的嘴脸
I saw who you are when no one's looking.
我看到那晚你付出的代价
And I saw what that night cost you.
Milton 你
Milton,
这是自找难堪啊
you're embarrassing yourself.
你强迫我女儿下跪
You forced my daughter on her knees,
结果她让你付出了代价
and she made you pay for it.
是吧 穿皮夹克的?
Isn't that right, Leather Jacket?
当时你在场
You were there.
这个混蛋让你发誓不告诉别人
Dickless made you swear not to tell anyone.
呦 John
Yo, John.
把孩子给我
Give me the child.
我说 把孩子给我
I said, give me the child.
不!
No!
后退!
Back off!
孩子 对我来说 一边吃着葡萄柚当早餐 一边给你喉咙来一枪
My child, it'd be pretty easy for me to shoot you in the throat,
看你血汨汨地流 那很简单
watch you gurgle, while I eat my morning grapefruit.
但我不想这样 Piper 你...
But I don't think so, Piper. You...
你让我感兴趣
You interest me.
我可以杀了你
I could take your life.
我也可以庇佑你
Or I could bestow my blessings upon you.
教你 就像教Milton的女儿那样
Teach you, like I taught Milton's daughter.
你让我想起她 知道吗?
You remind me of her, you know?
如此神似
So much spirit.
但我毁了她
But I broke her.
而且我很乐意用相同的方式毁了你
And I will so enjoy breaking you the same way.
上车走
Let's go for a ride.
走!
Let's go!
不! 不!
No! No!
不! Milton! Milton!
No! Milton! Milton!
我他妈的一定会杀了你!
I'll fucking kill you!
操! 操! 放开我!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Get off me!
不! 不! 他妈的放开我 你他妈个混账!
No! No! Fucking get off me, you motherfucker!
这下有乐子了!
This is gonna be fun!
- 风骚娘们! 风骚娘们!  - 我们坐车去 骚货
- Feisty bitch! Feisty bitch!  -  We're going for a ride, girl.
看见这根腿骨了吗?
You see this here femur bone?
是你女儿的
That belonged to your daughter.
无论去哪儿 我都随身带着
I keep it with me wherever I go.
操! 操! 操! 操蛋放我走!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you! Fucking let me go!
下次 我会射穿你这张臭嘴
Next time, I'll shoot you in your fucking mouth.
可以走了吗?
Shall we proceed?
我们得把他们埋到外面去
We'll bury them out back.
你现在去卡车那儿 把他妈的铲子拿来
Now, get the fucking shovels out of the truck.
不 你他妈的自己拿去吧
No, you go get the fucking shovels.
操!
Fuck!
走! 快走! 趴下!
Go! Go! Down!
他怎么还没挂?
How come he ain't dead?
没事 我马上干掉他
It don't matter. He's gonna be.
哦 看看
Well, look at this.
他还在追
He's still coming.
- 谁还在追?  - Milton
- Who's still coming?  - Milton.
- Milton  - 想干吗?
- Milton.  - What?
- 乖乖坐着  - 他还活着
- Stay down.  - He's alive.
你可是爆了他的头啊
But you shot him in the face.
你们还不懂吗?
Don't you see?
我们正站在命运的十字路口
We stand at a crossroads.
你们都没感觉到吗 我们终于可以大展拳脚
Y'all didn't think we could just kick up our heels,
改变这世界了 不是吗?
and change the world, did you?
嗯
Mmm-mmm.
战斗即将来临 神圣的战斗
We got a fight coming. A glorious battle.
他超过去了!
He's coming around!
去死吧!
Fuck you!
看我不把你弄死 你个小贱人!
I'm going to kill you, you little bitch!
我改主意了 Piper
I've changed my mind about you, Piper.
你实在是太任性 我都没法教了
You are too willful to be taught.
我要杀了你
I am going to kill you,
然后慢慢奸尸
and then I'm going to defile your corpse.
从现在开始
Between now and then,
我会让你吃不了兜着走
I'm gonna fuck you up.
噢 Piper
Oh, Piper.
倒拔垂柳!
Knock her ass out!
你真是太任性了
You're so willful.
叫你任性!
Willful!
安息吧 亲爱的Piper
Goodbye, sweet Piper.
他冲着我们来了!
He's coming right at us!
Piper 跳!
Piper!
天啊 Milton 怎么回事?
Jesus, Milton. How?
它还在里面
It's still in there.
子弹 我能... 我能感觉到
The bullet. I can... I can feel it.
那你怎么会还活着?
How are you still alive?
没时间解释了 他们要跑远了
We don't have time for this. They're getting away.
我以为你已经死了
Thought you were dead.
这驾照岂止是过期 都能算得上是古董了
This license isn't just expired, it's antique.
她告诉大家 你已经死了
She told everyone you were dead.
你在监狱蹲了多久?
How long were you in prison?
还是你根本没进去过?
Were you in prison at all?
我的天 Milton 你跟我说过真话吗?
Jesus, Milton, has anything you told me been true?
我以前认识个住在这附近的人 你有
I used to know a guy who lived out this way. You have one of those
便携式电话吗?
portable phones?
手机? 你是说手机是吧 Milton?
A cell phone? You mean a cell phone, Milton?
是啊 我有个手机 在我手提包里
Yeah, I got a cell phone. It's in my purse.
- 你就想这么糊弄我吗?  - 能就好了
- You just gonna ignore me?  - I'm gonna try.
我们得把这车藏起来 我来推 你把方向盘
We have to hide the car. I'll push, you steer.
做梦吧 谁在乎?
Forget about it. Who cares?
你在乎 你杀了2个警察
You should. You killed two cops.
# 车内气氛 快要燃烧 #
# Here we are burning up in our cars #
# 心亦如此 #
# and in our hearts #
# 喝你泡的茶 好运如破晓 #
# With your tea. Lucky states as the day breaks #
# 问道于盲者 #
# The blind are leading the blind #
- 今天挺热啊 是吧?  - 救救我
- Scorcher today, huh?  - Help me.
天呐 不好意思
Christ on a cracker. My apologies.
那个代表什么?
What's that supposed to mean?
那是我们与真主撒旦契约的印记
It's a symbol of our pact with Lord Satan.
契约 是吗? 噢!
Pact, huh? Ooh!
可笑 他可从没提到过你
Funny, he's never mentioned you.
喔! 真是糟糕啊 来 喝点水吧
Whoa! Those are fucked. Here, have some water.
真是业余
Amateurs.
我会死 是吗?
I'm gonna die, ain't I?
- Milton的东西 我拿走了  - 好
- Milton's work, I take it.  - Yeah.
狗娘养的 快打死我!
Son of a bitch shot me!
等等 你怎么...
Wait. How did you...
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是"会计师"
I'm The Accountant.
我很好奇 我一般不会对什么好奇
I'm curious, and I never get curious.
- 你们这些人想从Milton身上得到什么?  - 你谁啊?
- What do you people want with Milton?  - You're the who?
这很重要吗? Milton对你们而言 为什么这么重要?
Does it matter? Milton. Why is he important to you?
重要个屁! 是他一直追着我们!
He isn't! He's the one chasing us!
- 为什么?  - 因为...
- Why?  - Because...
因为我们所做的 我们所夺走的
Because of what we did. Because of who we took.
好吧 我真的很好奇 你们做了什么? 你们又夺走了谁?
Well, color me curious, what did you do? And who did you take?
弄痛你了 就跟我说 Milton
Let me know if I hurt you, Milton.
我刚才想把她抢回来的
I tried to get her back.
真的
I really did.
我知道
I know.
去他妈的恶魔崇拜者 他们真他妈让我抓狂
Fucking devil worshippers. They freak me the fuck out.
他们不该动用那些力量的 现在却随便动用 快气死我了
Messing with powers they ought not to. Turns my shit white.
这些都是虚幻的
None of it's real.
Milton 不是的 UFO 大脚野人 还有鬼都是扯淡的
No, Milton. UFOs and bigfoot and ghosts, that's bullshit.
恶魔是真的
Devils and demons.
一旦你开启了那些门 就由不得你关上了
Once you open those doors, you just can't close them.
你知道的 不是吗?
But you know that, don't you?
- 你不是死了吗  - 噢 这话我们最近听多了
- You're dead.  - Yeah, we've been getting that a lot lately.
不 小姑娘
No, toots.
我还搬过他的棺材
I carried his coffin.
Webster啊
Webster,
你是要继续握着那把.357口径手枪 还是把它拿出来?
are you gonna keep stroking that .357, or you gonna yank it?
那要看情况了
That depends.
你怎么会还活着?
How is this possible?
你听说过我的女儿吗?
You heard about my daughter?
是的
I did.
那你应该知道我为什么回来
Then you know why I'm back.
我不太明白...
I don't...
麻烦你解释一下 好吗?
Can you explain this, please?
他很爱他的女儿
He loved his daughter.
哪个父亲不爱自己的女儿
A lot of daddies love their daughters.
但这不能解释这个令人震惊的现实
But it don't explain shattering reality.
那家伙太爱自己的女儿了 以至于女儿开始恨他
Well, that one loved his little girl enough to make her hate him.
呃 他...
Uh, he was...
他是个非常 非常不称职的丈夫
He was a bad, bad husband.
但他却是个好父亲
But he was a good father.
后来 我们入错了伙
And then, we went and got mixed up in the wrong crowd.
一旦陷进去 就无法脱身了
And once you are in, there ain't no getting out.
所以为了保护她 在她还高中时 他就销声匿迹了
So, to protect her, he vanished while she was still in high school.
我也随他一起去了
And I went with him.
- 但你逃出来了  - 是的
- But you got out.  - Yeah, I did.
不过那是因为 任务完成的时候 有几个人
But only 'cause he paid a little visit to some fellows
想灭了我们 他去见了那些人
who wanted to kill us when the job was done.
他一个人去了 你明白吧 早知道我也该去的
He went alone, you see. I would've gone,
但我当时不知道
but I didn't know.
我是该去的
I would've gone.
这火让你回想到地狱了?
That fire making you homesick?
冰啤酒要吗?
Cold beer?
火焰并不是最可怕的部分
Fire isn't the worst part.
火焰中的画面才是
It's the video feed.
不是你自己所受的苦难
It's not about your suffering,
煎熬
your burning.
而是你爱的人承受的痛苦 因为
It's about the suffering of those you love because
你可以看得
that's all you see
一清二楚
in full detail.
你只能眼睁睁地看着
And there's nothing you can do to shut it off.
我被杀那年女儿才16岁
My daughter was 16 when I got shot.
我看着她落泪
I watched her weep.
我听着她骂我
I watched her curse me.
我看着她加入邪教
I watched her join that cult.
我看着那些凶手
I watched the murders.
先是杀害我的从不惹事 自由自在的女婿 然后...
My tree-hugging, sandal-wearing son-in-law first, and then...
然后是我的女儿
And then my daughter.
地狱的煎熬
Burning is nothing
比起看着自己孩子的头被人拧下来 又算得了什么
compared to watching your child's head being torn off.
谢谢你 Webster 我现在不会去喝那杯冰啤酒
Thank you, Webster. I don't believe I'll be having that beer just now.
直到我能拧下Jonah King的头盖骨 用它盛来喝
Not unless I'm drinking it from Jonah King's skull.
John 那车我恐怕修不好了
John, I can't fix that car.
但我能让你去你要去的地方
But I can get you where you need to be.
Milton 如果我没记错的话
Milton, if memory serves,
你以前可是和这辆雪佛兰人车合一的 是吗?
you were always partial to the Chevelle, yes?
- 454的?  - 是啊
- 454?  - Yeah.
- 这里是911  - 你好
- 9-1-1.  - Hi.
- 您有什么紧急状况?  - 昨晚有人
- What's your emergency?  - About that fella
在猛牛酒吧杀了里面所有的人
who killed all them people at the Bull By The Balls last night.
先生?
Sir?
我知道在哪找到他
I know where you can find him.
Stillwater Marsh监狱很多年以前就关闭了
Stillwater Marsh Penitentiary shut down ages ago.
想猜猜助祭树是什么吗?
You wanna guess what Deacon's Tree was?
- 用来施绞刑的树  - 猜对了
- Hanging tree.  - Yeah.
上一次绞刑是在38年 他们留下了那棵树用来奚落囚犯
Last hanging was in '38. They left the tree to taunt the inmates.
谷歌地图说 开车要8小时
Google Maps says it's an eight-hour drive.
- 我们会在...  - Webster
- We should be...  - Webster,
- 我要你留下来  - 什么?
- I need you to stay here.  - What?
不行 你上次就是一个人去的
No. You went alone last time.
这次不是
I'm not going alone.
你是要带那个小萝莉 不带我吗?
Are you gonna take that little girl over me?
把弹壳都给我吧
Give me the shells.
你真是个该死的矛盾体 你知道吗?
You're a goddamned walking contradiction, you know that?
你有多少次想要伸张正义
How many times you walk towards the straight and narrow
最后却以牺牲别人而收场?
only to get covered up in someone else's blood?
你这次又要以谁生命终结来收场?
Whose blood are you gonna end up covered in this time?
- 这次不一样  - 是吗?
- This time it's different.  - Is it?
他不一起来吗?
He's not coming?
Piper啊
Piper,
我需要你 但我不会对你说谎
I need you. But I won't lie to you.
这事很难办
This is going to be rough.
你确定要跟我一起吗?
Are you sure about this?
一直以来 我的生活除了等待一无所有
My whole life has been nothing but waiting.
等人点餐 等一个混蛋 我一直等着生活有意义的那一天
Waiting on tables, waiting on fools, waiting for it just to mean something.
现在 终于让我等到了
And now, it means something.
我跟定你了
I'm with you until the end.
我们现在干吗?
What do we do?
没事
Nothing yet.
该死
Shit.
你们只要把他们逼向这边 剩下的交给我们
You just keep driving them to us. We'll do the rest.
记得在爆炸之前脱身
And make sure you peel off before the fireworks.
警官们 集合!
Troopers, fall in!
大家听好 这两个人杀了两个我们的人
Gentlemen, these two have killed two of our own.
我知道你们很想让他们偿命
I know you want to make them pay.
所以 当我下令瞄准轮胎时
Therefore, when I tell you to aim for their tires,
就是在说
what I mean is
瞄准他们的脑袋 都明白了吗?
aim for their heads. Are we clear?
是 长官!
Yes, sir!
很好
Very well then.
现在
Please,
瞄准轮胎
aim for their tires.
前面会有更多
There'll be even more ahead.
继续开吧
Just keep driving.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
来了
Here we go.
穷途末路了 伙计
End of the line, folks.
举起双手 慢慢走出车子
Step out of the vehicle with your hands raised.
还是给他们的轮胎干净利落来一枪
May as well give the boys a clear shot
比较好
at their tires.
氢气
未来能源
那到底是什么?
What the hell is that?
噢 不速之客嘛
Well, this is unexpected.
所有人 都让开!
Everybody, clear the road!
闪开!
Get out of here!
趴下
Get down.
把枪给我!
Give me that thing!
要不要打爆他的轮胎 长官?
You want us to shoot out his tires, Captain?
他妈的不是吧
No goddamn way.
老天真不给面子 偏偏在这个时候出现一个联邦调查员
No ever loving way in God's good heaven are you an FBI agent.
我命令你们退下
I need you boys to stand down.
长官 这张证件你懂的 是吧?
Captain, you know what this badge means, right?
联邦调查局 你他妈的别碍事
Federal Bureau of get-the-fuck-out-of-my-way.
我们联邦正在调查的案子 被你们这群人搅得一团糟
You boys have blundered into an ongoing Federal case.
现在 放下你们的武器
Now, lower your weapon.
- 你  - 嘿 嘿 嘿! 长官!
- You.  - Hey, hey, hey! Captain!
看来你是一仆侍奉二主啊
It seems you're serving two masters.
拿出你的电话 打给你主子
Take out your phone and call him.
打给Jonah King
Call Jonah King.
跟他说Milton已经死了
Tell him Milton is dead.
照他说的做 警员 你听到探员的命令了
Do as he says, Trooper. You heard the agent.
你们其他人 退下
The rest of you, stand down.
所有人立刻退下 该死的!
Everybody, stand down right now, God damn it!
他们为什么没来追我们?
Why aren't they following us?
因为你是个心狠手辣 名声在外的弑警杀手
Because you're a straight up, certifiable, cop-killing murderer,
他们怕你
and they're scared of you.
那现在呢?
So, what now?
开车
Now we drive.
# 与魔鬼同行 #
# Ride with the Devil #
# 和上帝同藏 #
# Hide with the Lord #
# 我没有枪 #
# I got no pistol #
# 也没有剑 #
# Ain't got no sword #
# 我没有武器 #
# I got no army #
# 也没有土地 #
# Ain't got no land #
# 我一无所有 除了手中的石块 #
# Ain't got nothing but the stone that's in my hand #
# 我手中的石块 #
# Stone in my hand #
# 我心中的爱慕 #
# All the love that's in my heart #
# 我手中的石块 #
# And the stone that's in my hand #
路易安娜州 Stillwater监狱
在这儿等我
Wait for me here.
Piper 你在哪?
Piper?
Milton 这儿
Milton.
- 放开她  - 我不想放
- Get away from her.  - I think not.
我用这个给你一枪 你知道后果怎样
I shoot you with this, you know what it means.
不论天堂还是地狱
No heaven, no hell.
你将不复存在了
You cease to exist.
该死 Milton 开枪
Damn it, Milton, shoot him.
你这是给我理由 把Piper小姐给逼死
All the more reason to keep Ms Piper in close proximity.
你倦了 Milton 你会再次迷失的
You are weary, Milton. You might miss again.
你以为你是谁?
Who the hell do you think you are?
死神吗?
Anubis?
你阻止不了我
You can't stop me.
阻止你?
Stop you?
Milton 要不是我 你都不会出现在这儿 你这个不知感恩的家伙
Milton, you wouldn't be here without me, you ungrateful shit.
之前的那个小小路障 就能阻止你了
That little roadblock back there, that would have stopped you.
所以 我要你把那个铁杀神枪放下
So, I want you to holster that iron God-killer,
然后说一声 "谢谢"
and say, "Thank you."
我说了 放下武器 还有说"谢谢"
I said, holster and "thank you."
不要伤害她
Don't hurt her.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在 解开皮带
Now, unbuckle the belt.
请放到这里
Right here, please.
啊 这样好多了
Ah, that's better.
你不是第一个逃出来的 但是我想你是最后一个了
You're not the first to get out, and I doubt you'll be the last,
但是我要知道
but I have got to know,
你是怎么偷走杀神枪的?
how did you get out with the God-killer?
我直接进去拿的
I just walked in and took it.
哦
Oh.
他一定很不想查出是你偷的
Wouldn't want to be you when he finds out.
他会怎么惩罚我? 不让我回去了吗?
What's he gonna do? Not let me back in?
- 你为什么帮我?  - 都是因为那帮混蛋
- Why are you helping me?  - It's 'cause of those crazy fucks.
他们找到了把地狱带到人间的方法!
They figured out how to bring hell to earth!
Milton 这是真的 Jonah就快得逞了
Milton, it's real. Jonah's gonna do it.
- 真有趣 你还没跟她说?  - 说什么?
- That's cute. You haven't told her?  - Told her what?
亲爱的Piper小姐 向你透露点小秘密
Young Ms Piper, let you in on a little secret.
黑魔头 撒旦 别西卜(都是圣经中堕落的魔王的别称)
The Dark Lord, Satan, Beelzebub,
路西法(魔王本名)
Lucifer,
简单来说 他掌管着一个巨大的监狱  事实上他是个安静的人
simply the warden of a very large prison. Quiet man, actually.
深思而博学
Thoughtful and he's well-read.
我碰巧了解到
I happen to know,
杀害婴孩向他献祭的做法 令他十分愤慨
the idea of sacrificing children in his honor annoys him greatly.
- 你究竟为什么帮我?  - 我也有自己的任务
- Why are you really helping me?  - We all have a job to do.
把你弄来这儿 我的任务就更好做了 你救出你的人
Getting you here makes my job easier. You get what you want,
- 我完成我的任务  - 那现在赶紧帮我
- I get what I want.  - Then help me now.
- 不  - 他们那边有40个人
- No.  - There are 40 of them down there,
- 你和我一起能...  - 不
- and you and I could...  - No.
你想救她吗 Milton? 那你得自己去 自己做
You want to save her, Milton? Then you go, and you do it.
你成功 我也就成功了
If you win, I win.
如果他们解决了你 我也成功了
If they take you down, I win.
希望你喜欢这场好戏
And I hope you like butter on your popcorn.
肯定是场精彩绝伦的打斗
It's sure to be a grand show.
你还不去? Milton 时间在渐渐地流逝 午夜快到了
You're still here? Milton, the clock's ticking. Midnight approaches,
- 圆月也已升起了  - 把钥匙给我
- and the moon is full.  - Give me the keys.
我就在这儿等你
I'll be right here.
我的信徒们
My children,
我们苦心孤诣
we have come so far
才到达这个地方 这个垂死的世界
to this place where the dying earth
将在我们脚下 瓦解它那腐坏的灵魂
bleeds its corrupt soul at our feet.
这个世界灭亡 我们就能得到重生
From its death, we shall all be reborn.
重生!
Reborn!
我们...
We...
我们以前一直被驱逐 被追捕
We have been cast out and hunted.
以后不会了!
But no more!
不会了
No more.
经过这次献祭
With this sacrifice,
我们不必再躲躲藏藏了
we shall no longer be shunned.
他们说温顺之人能成大器
They say the meek will inherit.
他们错了! 我们不是温顺之人! 我们是天命所归!
They lie! We are not meek! We are chosen!
很快 地狱的喽们都会听命于我们!
And soon, the hounds of perdition will howl at our command!
现在 只要我这把匕首刺下去
For now, with a single thrust of this dagger,
我们所有人都将重获自由!
we shall all be set free!
到底怎么回事?
What the fuck?
是他!
That's him!
快 抓住他!
Come on, let's get him!
来 拿好 不管如何 这小孩今晚都得死
Here, take it. No matter what, that child dies tonight.
听到我命令 你就一刀刺进她的喉咙
I tell you to, and you cut his throat.
就是他
That's him.
他们都是和Milton一伙的
They're both with Milton.
哦 是吗? 你们以为可以阻止这一切吗?
Oh, yeah? You think you can stop all this?
我们会杀了你的朋友 还有那个婴儿 然后我们就会获得永生
We're gonna kill your friend and the baby. And We're gonna live forever.
永生?
Forever?
如果对你来说 多活5秒就算永生 那你算是说对了
If forever to you is the next five seconds, then you would be right.
噢...
Well...
你做好准备
You be ready now.
如果我杀了你 你就带不走他了
If kill you, you can't take him.
还会有别人来 他总归要回去的
Someone else will come. Someone else always comes.
Piper 他偷那把枪 不是不想跟我回去
Piper, he didn't steal that to stop me.
他只是想让我行动慢些 他已经得偿所愿了
He stole it to slow me down. He's getting what he wanted.
去帮他吧
Go to him.
去吧 否则就迟了
Now, before it's too late.
握紧点 这枪后挫力可不小
Hold on tight. It has quite the kick.
嘿 狗杂种
Hey, dickless.
噢 这下都他妈毁了
Well, this has all gone to shit.
你要去哪儿? Milton?
Where are you going? Milton?
胜利还是属于我 老兄
The victory is still mine, friend.
把那孩子抱过来
Bring that baby over here now.
我要他亲眼目睹她被杀死
I want him to witness this.
我说把那个该死的孩子抱过来!
I said bring the fucking baby to me!
我要用你女儿唯一留下的东西 把你折磨至死
I'm gonna beat you to death with all that's left of your daughter.
你女儿恨死你了
A daughter who hated you.
你女儿 因 你 而 死!
The daughter who you let die!
那好吧
All right, then.
我只想让你知道 我要你女儿的死 相对这个婴儿
I just want you to know that your daughter's death will pale
将面临的一切 简直太幸福了
to what is about to befall this child.
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you.
啊 Milton 你已经试过无数次了
Ah, Milton, so many have tried.
但我拥有的力量 你永远都不会了解
But I am armored with a power that you will never know.
这个世界上没有什么能杀死我
Nothing of this earth can kill me.
我不是这个世界的
I'm not of this earth.
Milton啊
Milton.
Milton啊!
Milton!
- 不 Milton  - 她在哪儿?
- No, Milton.  - Where is she?
我很好奇
I'm curious,
你当时会让他那么做吗?
would you have let him do it?
正如我所想
That's what I thought.
待会儿见
See you soon.
她在这儿
She's here.
我终于圆满了
I am finished now.
好好保护她
Keep her safe.
谁要是想伤害她 我就杀了他们
Anyone tries to hurt her, I'll kill them.
我知道
I know it.
所以我才选了你
That's why I chose you.
Webster会在有生之年
Webster will look out for you both,
照顾好你俩
as long as he can.
不 Milton
No, Milton.
Milton 求你 不要走
Milton, please, don't go.
代我去爱她 Piper
Love her for me, Piper.
爱她 把她当亲生女儿对待
Love her, and make her yours.
我知道我无权要你发誓
I know I don't have a right to ask for your promise.
我发誓 Milton 我发誓
I promise. Milton, I promise.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不
No.
嘿
Hey.
走吧
Come on.
嗨
Hi.
- 刚才那出怎么样?  - 我见过更精彩的
- How was that?  - I've seen better.
我想 她还不了解 你能
Guess she doesn't know you can
打败他 遏制他 击中他 甚至阻止他
beat him, slow him, shoot him, even stop him.
但死人永远都杀不死
But you can't kill a dead man.
可以走了吗?
Shall we?
即使地狱也有怜悯之心
Even in hell there is compassion.
我只想你知道 我没准备好好待着
Just so you know, I don't plan on staying.
Milton 你已经得偿所愿了
Milton, you got what you wanted.
当然 但如果他还把我关回那个洞里 我还是会逃出来
I did, but if he puts me back in that hole, I'll still get out.
很好
Remarkable.
实际上 我盼望着那一天的到来
I actually look forward to that.
你以为你是沃坦(北欧神话主神)啊?
You think you're Wotan?
把车钥匙给我
Give me the keys.
# 我还活着 #
# I'm still alive #
# 必有奇迹 #
# Must have been a miracle #
# 这段地狱之旅 #
# It's been a hell of ride #
# 前路充满未知 #
# Destination still unknown #
# 生活真实面目 #
# It's a fact of life #
# 性命攸关 不能踏错一步 #
# If you make one wrong move with the gun to your head #
# 不能回头 否则只剩死路 #
# You better walk the line or you'll be left for dead #
# 破旧轨道 执意脱轨前行 #
# I'm a runaway train on broken track #
# 倒数计时 永远附着炸弹 #
# I'm a ticker on a bomb that you can't turn back this time #
# 这是真的 #
# That's right #
# 逃过浩劫 我还顽强生存 #
# I got away with it all and I'm still alive #
# 世界崩塌 就让末日来临 #
# Let the end of the world come tumbling down #
# 我仍会是 最后坚定的人 #
# I'll be the last man standing on the ground #
# 只要还有 我的热血涌动 #
# As long as I got blood rush through my veins #
# 我就顽强生存 #
# I'm still alive #